Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Photograph Collection
1850s-2000s
New York University Archives
New York University
PHOTO.00001
478 Linear Feet in 478 boxes
The collection contains photographs that document the history of New York University and it surrounding environs, especially Washington Square Park and Greenwich Village. It includes images associated with NYU's various component schools and its former University Heights campus (now Bronx Community College).
Arrangement
The collection is organized into 33 series.
Provenance
The Photography Collection consists of photographs that were separated from university administrative collections or received as part of regular accessions from the University Photo Bureau. The Photo Bureau was founded in 1952, and archived their own collections until the mid-1980s, when they began regularly transferring prints, contact sheets and negatives to the University archives. All prints received from the Photo Bureau and those separated from administrative collections were incoporated into existing subject-based series. The Washington Square Park and Washington Square Area series represent the subject categories selected by the University Archives for digitization in the Spring of 2008.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open without restrictions.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains photographs that document the history of New York University and it surrounding environs, especially Washington Square Park and Greenwich Village. It includes images associated with NYU's various component schools and its former University Heights campus (now Bronx Community College).
Related Material at the New York University Archives
Guide to the Records of the Washington Square Association, Inc. 1908-1979
Historical Note
The bulk of this collection contains photographic and print images of Washington Square Park and the surrounding area. Buildings that are part of New York University's Washington Square campus, extant as well as demolished are included in this collection.
There is a separate series for the the University Building, New York University's first permanent home. It was constructed on the northeast corner of the park between Washington Place and Waverly Place in 1833-34. Architects Ithiel Town, Alexander Jackson Davis, and James Dakin as well as NYU engineering professor David B. Douglass designed the university's first building in the Gothic Revival-style. This type of architectural style was meant to evoke the medieval buildings of Oxford and Cambridge and link the more modern and practical American curriculum the university was founded on to the long, rich tradition of English education.
Initially, the building was too large for the student body to fill so residential rooms, studios, and laboratories were rented out to a variety of artists and inventors including Winslow Homer and Samuel F.B. Morse. In the late 19th century as the university expanded, the undergraduate college moved to the more spacious University Heights campus in the Bronx initially leading to the decline of the Washington Square campus and in 1894 the University Building was demolished. It was replaced by Main Building (now the Silver Center).
Sources:
"The University Building." The University Quarterly 17 (May 1894): 116-123. "University Building." New York University Education Quarterly (Spring 1981): 20.
Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.); Washington Square (New York, N.Y.); Aerial photographs; Photographs.; New York University -- Buildings
- Washington Square Park
  Scope and Content Note
  This series contains photographs and prints of Washington Square Park as well as the structures surrounding the four sides of the Park.
  - Subseries A: Aerial Views
    - Aerial Views, 1890s, 1890-1899, 2001, undated (Box 206, Folder 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1907; wsp_av_1_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking South, circa 1890; wsp_av_1_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 1, Item 2)
        Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1890; wsp_av_1_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Aerial Views, 1900-1919 (Box 206, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1919; wsp_av_1_2_01; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Aerial Views, 1920s, 1920-1929 (Box 206, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1926; wsp_av_1_3_01; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1913; wsp_av_1_3_02; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, circa 1920; wsp_av_1_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, circa 1926; wsp_av_1_3_04; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, circa 1926; wsp_av_1_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, circa 1926; wsp_av_1_3_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, 1926; wsp_av_1_3_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, 1926; wsp_av_1_3_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Aerial Views, 1930s, 1930-1939 (Box 206, Folder 4)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1930-1939; wsp_av_1_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1934; wsp_av_1_4_02; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1939; wsp_av_1_4_03; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1930-1939; wsp_av_1_4_04; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1937; wsp_av_1_4_05; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_06; Sozio, A.F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_07; Sozio, A.F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1938; wsp_av_1_4_10; Jackson, Edward E.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Aerial Views, 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 206, Folder 5)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking South, circa 1940-1949; wsp_av_1_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1947; wsp_av_1_5_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking East, circa 1940-1949; wsp_av_1_5_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1940; wsp_av_1_5_04; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 4)
        Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.); Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1943; wsp_av_1_5_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area, Aerial View, 1947; wsp_av_1_5_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 5, Item 6)
        Aerial photographs
    - Aerial Views, 1946-50, 1946-1950 (Box 206, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946; wsp_av_1_6_01; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 1)
        Washington Square (New York, N.Y.); Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_02; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_03; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1947; wsp_av_1_6_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking South, 1949; wsp_av_1_6_05; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946; wsp_av_1_6_06; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_07; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_08; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950; wsp_av_1_6_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_10; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1949; wsp_av_1_6_11; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1946-1950; wsp_av_1_6_12; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 6, Item 12)
    - Aerial Views, 1950s, 1950-1959 (Box 206, Folder 7)
      - Washington Square Park Aerial View, wsp_av_1_7_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_1_7_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1953; wsp_av_1_7_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - Winter Scene, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950-1959; wsp_av_1_7_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - Winter Scene, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950; wsp_av_1_7_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1953; wsp_av_1_7_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950-1959; wsp_av_1_7_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1954; wsp_av_1_7_08; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1959; wsp_av_1_7_09; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1953; wsp_av_1_7_10; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1954; wsp_av_1_7_11; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_1_7_12; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 12)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1954; wsp_av_1_7_13; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 13)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_14; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 14)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_15; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 15)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_16; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 16)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_17; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 17)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_18; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 18)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1950; wsp_av_1_7_19; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 19)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1950; wsp_av_1_7_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 20)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_1_7_21; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 21)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1952; wsp_av_1_7_22; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 22)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking West, 1951; wsp_av_1_7_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 7, Item 23)
    - Aerial Views, 1960s (Folder 1 of 2), 1960-1969 (Box 206, Folder 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960; wsp_av_1_8_01; Fairchild Aerial Surveys, inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_1_8_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1965; wsp_av_1_8_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - Cars, Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_05; Thomas Airviews; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area, Aerial View, Looking South, 1964; wsp_av_1_8_07; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_08; Thomas Airviews; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1965; wsp_av_1_8_09; Thomas Airviews; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_1_8_10; Thomas Airviews; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_11; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_1_8_12; Giese, Al; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1963; wsp_av_1_8_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1964; wsp_av_1_8_14; Seligson, Stanley; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 206, Folder 8, Item 14)
    - Aerial Views, 1960s (Folder 2 of 2), 1960-1969 (Box 207, Folder 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 4 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_02; Thomas Airviews; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_03; Thomas Airviews; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_04; Thomas Airviews; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1969; wsp_av_2_1_05; Skyviews Survey, Inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1966; wsp_av_2_1_06; Thomas Airviews; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_07; Thomas Airviews; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_08; Aero Service Corporation; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1969; wsp_av_2_1_09; Skyviews Survey, Inc.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1964; wsp_av_2_1_10; Seligson, Stanley; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 10)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960's; wsp_av_2_1_11; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 11)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, wsp_av_2_1_12; Mal Gurian Associates (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 12)
      - New York University Buildings, Washington Square Area, Aerial View, 1967; wsp_av_2_1_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 13)
        Aerial photographs; Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 14)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking North, 1963; wsp_av_2_1_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 15)
      - Washington Square Area and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, circa 1960-1969; wsp_av_2_1_16; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 16)
        Washington Square (New York, N.Y.); Aerial photographs
      - Washington Square Park, Looking Southwest, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_17; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 17)
      - Washington Square Park, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_18; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 18)
      - Washington Square Park, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_19; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 19)
      - Washington Square Arch, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_20; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 20)
      - Washington Square Park, circa 1967; wsp_av_2_1_21; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 21)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 22)
        New York (N.Y.).; Washington Square (New York, N.Y.)
      - Manhattan Skyline and Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1968; wsp_av_2_1_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 23)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1966; wsp_av_2_1_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 24)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1965; wsp_av_2_1_25; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 1, Item 25)
    - Aerial Views, 1965 Shadow Study (Box 207, Folder 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1965; wsp_av_2_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 207, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1965; wsp_av_2_2_02 (Box 207, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1965; wsp_av_2_2_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 207, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Looking North, 1965; wsp_av_2_2_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 207, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Aerial Views, 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 207, Folder 3)
      - Washington Square Park, Aerial View, Looking Southwest, 1970; wsp_av_2_3_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 207, Folder 3, Item 1)